[{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980245033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12999,"timeElapsed":56465},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980265439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":20403,"timeElapsed":76870},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":54736,"timeElapsed":131608},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":11068,"timeElapsed":142678},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4861,"timeElapsed":147541},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":34347,"timeElapsed":181891},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6309,"timeElapsed":188202},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5394,"timeElapsed":193598},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4466,"timeElapsed":198067},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":15367,"timeElapsed":214389},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2862,"timeElapsed":217252},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2534,"timeElapsed":219788},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1686,"timeElapsed":221477},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1824,"timeElapsed":223303},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3205,"timeElapsed":226510},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":228126},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2628,"timeElapsed":230756},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":233007},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4650,"timeElapsed":238526},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1922,"timeElapsed":240450},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":242680},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1905,"timeElapsed":244587},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":246698},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1774,"timeElapsed":248474},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1493,"timeElapsed":249968},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1412,"timeElapsed":251382},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":253695},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":12814,"timeElapsed":267454},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4015,"timeElapsed":271471},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980462720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":274152},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468474,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5752,"timeElapsed":279906},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3084,"timeElapsed":282992},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":286006},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":288195},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2139,"timeElapsed":290336},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2357,"timeElapsed":292695},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2691,"timeElapsed":295388},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":34461,"timeElapsed":331167},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2390,"timeElapsed":333559},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2874,"timeElapsed":336435},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2309,"timeElapsed":338747},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1759,"timeElapsed":340508},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536705,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7627,"timeElapsed":348137},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":10634,"timeElapsed":358772},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2113,"timeElapsed":360887},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1856,"timeElapsed":362746},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980553818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":365250},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5622,"timeElapsed":372168},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2284,"timeElapsed":374454},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":377412},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2186,"timeElapsed":379601},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":381451},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":383964},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1517,"timeElapsed":385483},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3197,"timeElapsed":388682},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1937,"timeElapsed":390622},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6357,"timeElapsed":397796},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3182,"timeElapsed":400980},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2333,"timeElapsed":403315},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3658,"timeElapsed":406975},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":409536},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2971,"timeElapsed":412509},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2884,"timeElapsed":415395},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3827,"timeElapsed":419223},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3731,"timeElapsed":422956},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5692,"timeElapsed":429492},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3786,"timeElapsed":433281},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980623917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":435349},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":437369},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1743,"timeElapsed":439114},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":441344},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":443082},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3634,"timeElapsed":446717},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2656,"timeElapsed":449375},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":17381,"timeElapsed":467535},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":469695},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":471592},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2196,"timeElapsed":473789},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2001,"timeElapsed":475793},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2820,"timeElapsed":478614},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":480311},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2210,"timeElapsed":482523},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":1703,"timeElapsed":484228},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6447,"timeElapsed":491487},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2145,"timeElapsed":493634},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":496890},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1945,"timeElapsed":498837},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1824,"timeElapsed":500663},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1961,"timeElapsed":502625},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1598,"timeElapsed":504225},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1654,"timeElapsed":505882},{"subjectID":"jb0lnog8g5","prolificID":"6665b652ecac3856fcb26a6a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b255daa828312e3e7d01","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2874,"timeElapsed":508758}]